







# **Brent O'Hagan**

{Visual Media Producer & Digital Designer}

# professional profile

A Visual Media Producer and Digital Designer specializing in online video production for brands Seven years of professional video experience working within the online environment Two and a half years working with major brands, launching in-house video

Portfolio & Demo: http://www.brentohagan.com

# work history highlights

### Video Designer & Editor, Hootsuite

Present (1.5 yrs)

Member of the in-house content team responsible for video campaigns based around a social media management platform. Responsibilities include preproduction, videography, video editing, motion graphic design, channel and systems management as well as video archiving.

# **Video Designer & Editor**, Arc'teryx Equipment Inc.

2011 - 2012 (1 yr)

Member of the in-house marketing team responsible for producing video campaigns for high-end outdoor clothing company. Responsibilities included preproduction, videography, video editing, motion graphic design, channel and systems management as well as video archiving.

#### Visual Media Producer & Digital Designer, Fountain Hill

2009 - Present (5 yrs)

Freelancer specializing in the production of online video content for brands. Selected client list: Arc'teryx, Norco Bikes, BC Health, BC Parks, Alias Cinema and Hootsuite.

#### Video Editor & Office Manager, Mike Wiegele Helicopter Skiing

2009 – 2010 (5 mos)

Seasonal position as video editor, photo retoucher and office manager to the visual media department .

## Founding Partner & Video Producer, VMG Cinematic

2007 - 2009 (2 yrs)

Video production company specializing in online advertising and corporate communications. Responsibilities included campaign design, project management, budgeting, videography, editing, motion graphics, hiring and management of employees. Selected client list: Ogilvy, DHL, HP, Intel and Harley-Davidson.

## education

**SUCCESS School of Business**, Certificate, Small Business Operations, Marketing and Management 2010 – 2011 **Sheridan College**, Post Graduate Certificate, Advanced Television and Film Production 2005 – 2006 **The University of Western Ontario**, Honours Bachelor of Arts, Film Studies 2001 – 2005